thetelemarketingforum.com 2018-11-02

# Privacy Policy - SafeSoft Solutions

### Privacy Policy

**SafeSoft Solutions Privacy Statement**

SafeSoft Solutions has created this privacy policy to explain how and what information we collect when you use our site or our services and how that information is used.  If you have any questions, please email us [here](mailto:info@safesoftsolutions.com).

**Types of Information We Collect**

Like most other websites, the SafeSoft Solutions Site is structured to collect information when you use the site and then when you register or sign in to use the SafeSoft Solutions Services.  This applies also if you are using a mobile device.

_Non-personal Information._   When you visit the SafeSoft Solutions site, we collect non-personal information, which is information about things like your IP address, browser and operating system.  This is done through “cookies,”  which are small files with unique ID numbers to simplify your logging in and staying logged into a website and using services there, such as the SafeSoft Solutions Site and the SafeSoft Solutions Services.  Our cookies do not allow us to learn your real name and address.

_Personal Information._   We receive more detailed personally-identifiable information from you when you register to use the SafeSoft Solutions Services, authorize payment or do something like sign up for a newsletter or seek technical support.  Naturally, this information could include your name, email address, credit card information and such other information that could identify you.

_Advertising Information._   Some information created by cookies involves how users such as you navigate the SafeSoft Solutions Site.  That information is also used by third party services we use such as Google search and display advertising services.  We use Google’s remarketing feature, through the Google Display Network, to inform, optimize and serve relevant and useful ads based on past visits to our website. This service enables us to modify ads presented based on that information.  This requires the use of first-party cookies, and third-party cookies placed on our SafeSoft Solutions Site. Those services do not enable us to identify you.  You can change your browser setting, as described below.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

We use the information in several ways, among them:  to simplify your login;  to  improve the SafeSoft Solutions Services, including customizing them to your preferences;  to respond to technical support requests;  to enable payment for your use of the services;  and to inform you of certain changes in the services.  We may transfer the data across state and country borders for the purposes of data consolidation, storage and simplified customer information management.  When you register with us you consent to receiving marketing materials from SafeSoft Solutions.  You can opt out of receiving such materials through the procedures included in them.

We don’t sell or trade your personal information.  We don’t share the personal information except for limited purposes of running our business by using the services of third parties that have agreed with us to keep such information secure.  These would include, for example, cloud storage providers, email services for newsletters and the like. We may have to disclose information if we believe that it is appropriate or necessary for legal reasons (such as a government request, court order or legal process served on us).  You consent to such disclosure.

The SafeSoft Solutions Services enable you to use information about other individuals that you have obtained.  SafeSoft Solutions does not have access to such information except in situations where that information has caused, or is involved in, system malfunctions that would require us to access such information to examine it exclusively to solve the problem or there is a valid legal request from a government authority.  You, not SafeSoft Solutions, are responsible for the use of such information in compliance with all relevant rules and regulations.

**Opting Out of Third Party Cookies**

Your browser may be set to a default that accepts cookies, but usually you can modify those settings to reject cookies.  If you do so, please understand that some of the features of the SafeSoft Solutions Services or parts of the SafeSoft Solutions Site might be disabled.  You can also opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Google Ads Preference Manager.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg4FCJO_UFgbAm-R4DHVvw6Z85Zd5NhIlURUiIPE2-Sep8Z--It_B5omX03neeu3OSac6VfycvmQSaBHsA8qU9A0-hJQip8bwtfunF0r9qlyQ_O06K4yzmN0HurA3Kj5NmQk6Mn9n2rysjklOpAB4es7ks3-xqESldbWcyfMp_2k_jD6dA&hl=en)

**Links to Other Sites**

The SafeSoft Solutions Site may from time to time include links to third party sites.  When you visit those sites you are subject to their privacy policies and practices and SafeSoft Solutions is not responsible for those sites or anything on them or available through them.  You should review and understand the privacy policy of each such site.

**Do Not Track Notice**

SafeSoft Solutions does not respond to Do Not Track signals because, except for the Google analytic services described above, SafeSoft Solutions does not track site visitors across third party sites and over time to provide targeted advertising.  Your browser should be able to set the Do Not Track signal on sites that do respond, thereby enabling you to inform them that you are not to be tracked.

**For Users Outside the US**

If you live outside the United States, there may be other privacy and disclosure requirements.  However, by using the SafeSoft Solutions Site you agree and consent to us collecting, processing and transferring data about you in accordance with this privacy policy solely under the applicable laws of California, where we provide the SafeSoft Solutions Services.  You are solely responsible for compliance with any data security or privacy obligations in your jurisdiction.

**Data Security**

SafeSoft Solutions complies with the requirements under California and federal law regarding data security.  If SafeSoft Solutions becomes aware of events governed by those laws then we will follow the procedures for notifying you.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We will advise you of changes to this privacy policy by noting the effective date of the most recent changes at the top of this page and in some cases by other means.  Those changes will affect your use of the SafeSoft Solutions Site and the SafeSoft Solutions Services going forward from that effective date.  The previous policies (which will be available through a link) will govern your use before the effective date.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments then please email us [here](mailto:info@safesoftsolutions.com).
